Guide to the Cornell University calendar collection, 1902-2005.
Cornell University calendar collection,
- Series II. Duplicates
  - 1995 Cornell Calendar, 1995 (Box 10)
    One duplicate; the cover features McGraw Tower at sundown; the large color photographs feature a wide variety of subjects from infamous Ithaca weather to student life to the Cornell campus; the photograph for February is unique, featuring "Ice Hockey in Lynah Rink;" the end of the calendar shows the image and publishing credits in addition to a calendar in brief of the previous and the following years; on the very back of the calendar is a short history of Cornell University.
  - Cornell Academic-Year Calendar 1995-1996, 1995-1996 (Box 10)
    Two duplicates; an academic-year calendar that covers the many academic, sports, and extracurricular events on campus from August 1996 to August 1997; the theme of this calendar is "Exploring Cornell" and, to complement, it includes "Did you know that ..." facts about the various buildings on campus (e.g. in February, "Did you know that ... the opening in the middle of the Johnson Museum building lets the afternoon sunlight reach the Arts Quad?"); the end of the calendar features the academic-year of 1996 to 1997 in brief; the back of the calendar includes publication credits.
  - Cornell Academic-Year Calendar 1996-1997, 1996-1997 (Box 10)
    One duplicate; an academic-year calendar that covers the many academic, sports, and extracurricular events on campus from August 1996 to August 1997; the theme of this calendar is "Exploring Cornell" and, to complement, it includes "Did you know that ..." facts about the various buildings on campus (e.g. in February, "Did you know that ... the opening in the middle of the Johnson Museum building lets the afternoon sunlight reach the Arts Quad?"); the end of the calendar features the academic-year of 1996 to 1997 in brief; the back of the calendar includes publication credits.
  - 1999 Cornell Calendar, 1999 (Box 10)
    One duplicate; the cover features "The Herbert F. Johnson Museum of Art" at twilight; the large color photographs feature a wide variety of subjects from infamous Ithaca weather to student life to major events (such as commencement) to the Cornell campus; the end of the calendar shows the image and publishing credits in addition to a calendar in brief of the previous and the following years; on the very back of the calendar is a short history of Cornell University.
  - 2001 Cornell Calendar, 2001 (Box 10)
    One duplicate; an academic-year calendar that covers the many academic, sports, and extracurricular events on campus from August 2001 to August 2002; features BW photographs of students or staff participating in the event listed and described at length at the photograph's side (e.g. in March, a photograph and short history of "Dragon Day" along with the dozens of events throughout the month); the end of the calendar features the academic-year of 2001 to 2002 in brief; the back of the calendar includes publication credits.
  - The Cornell Calendar 1914, 1914 (Box 10)
    Calendar is OVERSIZED. Includes one duplicate; the cover features a colored-in photograph of the "Goldwin Smith Entrance" in a golden frame; features BW (and blue) photographs of the gorges and buildings on campus for each month (with titles underneath).
  - Cornell 1932, 1932 (Box 10)
    Calendar is OVERSIZED. Includes three duplicates; one duplicate is missing the front and back covers making the leaves loose; features BW photographs (with titles underneath) of the Cornell campus and student-life; the photograph for June features the popular swimming hole in Beebe Lake under the bridge with swimmers, male and female.
  - Cornell 1933, 1933 (Box 10)
    Calendar is OVERSIZED. Includes two duplicates; features exceptional BW photographs (with titles underneath) of the Cornell campus and student-life; the photographs for June document the commencement of the previous year and includes a great photograph of "The Commencement Procession Wind[ing] Its Way Around Schoellkopf Field."